(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-28T23:36:36.869782",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
1 2 3 Go! Let's make it!
うまく行かない今日だって しょぼくれたって
Even on days when things don't go well, or when I'm down,
明日の明後日の未来の私にバトンを渡したら
if I pass the baton to the future me of tomorrow or the day after,
何だってやれそうだ
I feel like I can do anything!
落書きの中に光ってたあの想いを
The thought that was shining in the scribbles,
君とこうして交わして語り合えたなんて嘘みたいだな
sharing and talking with you like this feels like a dream.
もっと
More...
また描いてしるして
Draw and write it down again.
いつも通りの日常に ちょっと色が増えていく
Colors are gradually adding to our usual daily life.
うつむいた一歩でも 諦めず進むよ
Even with downcast steps, I will go on without giving up.
しようよ どんな世界だって飛べるから
Let's do it, because we can fly in any world,
お互いにバトンを繋ぎ合おう
connecting our batons to each other.
何度も何度も植えた種は
The seeds planted over and over again,
いつか大きな花を咲かせて
will someday bloom into big flowers.
大好きは楽しくなれる魔法さ
Loving it is a magic that makes things fun.
一瞬で向こう 昨日よりも加速してる
In an instant, we are accelerating faster than yesterday.
ちゃんと繋いでて
Hold on tight to me.
簡単じゃない日々の掛け声は
The call of days that are not easy,
いつも君が明るく放って支えてくれた
you always released it brightly to support me.
ずっと刻まれて光るよ
It will always be carved and shine.
2025.10.2 Thu
Thursday, October 2, 2025
with DJ ANKIMO
TOKINO SORA
2019 1st year
2020 2nd year
2021 3rd year
2022 4th year
2023 5th year
2024 6th year
8th Starry Bloomin' Anniversary Party
[Title: 8th Starry Bloomin' Anniversary Party]
最初から始まっちゃって
It's starting right from the beginning,
限界を突破しちゃって
and breaking through the limits!
キックオフだって
It's kickoff time,
ラッキーを呼ぼう
so let's summon some luck!
超特急の風
A super-express wind
聞こえてきちゃって
is blowing in and can be heard,
空中をスラスラ滑る
gliding smoothly through the air
スライドしながら
while sliding along.
もう一回？
One more time?
まだダメかい？
Not yet?
だってこの指止まれ
After all, gather around me!
タップすると招待
Tap to get your invitation.
まだまだ足りない
It's still not enough,
SOS頂戴
send me an SOS!
もう一回？
One more time?
もう待てない！
I can't wait any longer!
今すぐアップデート
Update right now!
タ・タ・タ・タ　アップデート
U-u-u-u-update!
最初から始まっちゃって
It's starting right from the beginning,
限界を突破しちゃって
and breaking through the limits!
ピコピコ音で聞かせてリズム
Let me hear the rhythm in beeps and boops!
アップデートを始めちゃって
Start the update,
シグナルを飛び越えちゃって
and leap over the signals!
液晶の中の心を撃てよ
Shoot through the heart inside the LCD screen!
送信ボタン
Hit the send button,
この声に乗せてよ
and carry it on this voice!
夢進行
Dream in progress,
ネットワークを飛び回ろう
let's fly all over the network!
飽きちゃったらこの感情
If I get tired of this feeling,
アナログだって変化して
even analog will change.
喜怒哀楽　最速で1秒
Emotions shifting in just one second!
止められないこの状態
I can't stop this state of mind,
終わんない繋がってよ脳内
it's endless, connect inside my brain!
バグに答え
Answering the bugs,
会いたくない？
don't you want to see me?
両手でバッテン
Making an X with both hands!
止められないこの状態
I can't stop this state of mind,
教えて
tell me!
アップデート
Update!
タ・タ・タ・タ　アップデート
U-u-u-u-update!
最初から始まっちゃって
It's starting right from the beginning,
限界もリンクしちゃって
and even the limits are linking up!
ピコピコの熱を感じるんだ
I can feel the warmth of the beeps!
暴走モードになっちゃって
Going into runaway mode,
ファイルを初期化しちゃって
and initializing the files!
君のハッピーをもっと教えてよ
Show me more of your happiness!
手を伸ばしてよ
Reach out your hand!
送信ボタン
Hit the send button,
この声を乗せてよ
and carry it on this voice!
夢進行
Dream in progress,
ネットワークを飛び回ろう
let's fly all over the network!
アップデート アップデート アップデート アップデート
Update! Update! Update! Update!
描いたキャンバスに
On the canvas I painted,
アンサーを求めて
seeking an answer,
まだ見ぬ色を信じて
believing in colors yet unseen.
一歩踏み出して
Take a step forward,
ここから始まったストーリー
the story that starts from here.
夢で見た景色は
The scenery seen in my dreams
憧れを叶えていく
is turning my aspirations into reality.
アップデート アップデート アップデート
Update! Update! Update!
この広い世界で
In this vast world,
お気に入りのキミと出会えた奇跡
the miracle of meeting my favorite you.
アップデート アップデート アップデート
Update! Update! Update!
夢の向こう目がけて
Aiming for the other side of my dreams,
きっと届く、届いて！
it'll surely reach, please reach!
世界は広がって
The world is expanding,
また明日をアップデート
updating tomorrow once again,
夢みたいな色で
in colors like a dream,
また追いかけ続けていく
I'll keep chasing after it.
チャレンジは止まらない
The challenge will never stop,
手と手を繋いで
hand in hand, connected.
アップデート アップデート アップデート
Update! Update! Update!
今もずっとここで
Still right here, always,
いつの日かキミが見つけてくれるように
so that someday, you will find me.
アップデート アップデート アップデート
Update! Update! Update!
いつまでも超えて
Surpassing it forever.
...の元へ 届いて
...and reach to where you are.
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting for you.
時が変わっても
Even if time changes...
同じ星が あなたへ向かう声と ぴったりと ともに
...the same star will align perfectly with my voice heading towards you.
寂しくても 何度でも 待っている
Even if I'm lonely, I will wait over and over again...
涙を 勇気に変えて
...turning my tears into courage...
ここまで 歩いてきた 私だから
...because I have walked all the way here.
私 待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I am waiting, waiting, waiting for you.
この広い空で
In this vast sky...
あの日から 響いた声が 旅を続けるように
...so that the voice echoing from that day can continue its journey.
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, I'm waiting, I'm waiting for you...
目指した場所で
...at our destination.
君の元へ 届いて
Reach to where you are,
夢をどうか 叶えて
and please make our dream come true.
みんな！この曲待ってたでしょ？
Everyone! You've been waiting for this song, right?
しっかり掛け声覚えてきてくれたよね？
You've practiced the call and response well, right?
一緒に「ふーふー！」って言って盛り上がっちゃおう！
Let's say "Fuu Fuu!" together and get hyped!
せーの！
Ready, set, go!
ふーふー！
Fuu-fuu!
せーの！
Ready, go!
ふーふー！
Fuu-fuu!
我らのソラの始まりは
The beginning of our sky...
触れた瞬間 アラララララ
...was the moment we touched, ah-la-la-la-la!
はぁ、これは困った！
Oh, we're in trouble!
二度と元には戻らない 大爆発
A big bang that can never be undone!
そして星が生まれまして
And then, stars were born...
呼吸の数だけポコポコ生まれる
...popping up as many times as we breathe.
あぁ、あなたと出会った
Ah, meeting you...
これは次元を揺るがす大発見
...was a discovery that shook dimensions!
このままハートぶち上げて
Keeping our hearts high...
どこまでも届いていけ
...let's reach as far as we can!
って言っちゃって
...or so I say!
さあ、さあ、さあ、駆け抜けたこのラブは
Now, now, now, this love we ran through...
あなたがね、今頃受信してた
...you must be receiving it about now.
してたっけ？
Or are you?
あなたに一直線
Straight towards you!
出会えた奇跡を 分かち合える
We can share the miracle of meeting.
ほら 目の前にずっとある
Look, it's always right in front of us.
一直線
Straight line!
このビッグバンを築いて
Build this big bang!
ららら...
La la la...
愛は地球規模に膨らんで こんなになってる
Love expands to a global scale, becoming like this!
ららら...
La la la...
お騒がせお騒がせは この恋のためになる
Making a scene, making a scene is all for this love.
ふーふー！
Fuu-fuu!
せーの！
Ready, go!
ふーふー！
Fuu-fuu!
お騒がせ あなたのハートにピース
Making a fuss, peace to your heart!
今更急に良い人みたいな顔して
Now you're suddenly acting like a good guy...
めちゃめちゃ大嫌い
...I hate you so much!
ちょっとの反応に嬉しがったり
Getting happy over the slightest reaction,
なんか動画出すだけで一喜一憂
and riding an emotional rollercoaster over every video post.
我らの星の活動は
The activity of our star...
割とトグって
...is rather turbulent...
あぁ、それは凄いな
...ah, that is amazing!
つまりあなたと私の恒星系
In short, it's our stellar system.
このままあなたを連れて
Taking you along just like this,
あなたを目がけて
and aiming straight for you...
って言っちゃった
...or so I said!
さあ、さあ、さあ、押し寄せたこのラブは
Now, now, now, this rushing love...
あなたがね、今頃受信してた
...you must be receiving it about now.
してたっか？
Did you?
この距離まで近づいて
Getting this close,
出会えた奇跡を 分かち合える
we can share the miracle of meeting.
ほら 目の前でずっと笑い合って
Look, we'll always laugh together in front of each other.
一直線
Straight line!
このビッグバンを築いて
Build this big bang!
ららら...
La la la...
愛は地球規模に膨らんで こんなになってる
Love expands to a global scale, becoming like this!
ららら...
La la la...
お騒がせお騒がせは この恋のためになる
Making a scene, making a scene is all for this love.
ふーふー！
Fuu-fuu!
せーの！
Ready, go!
ふーふー！
Fuu-fuu!
最後！
Last one!
ふーふー！
Fuu-fuu!
みんな！
Everyone!
見えてる？聞こえてる？
Can you see me? Can you hear me?
はい、というわけで今日も2日目！そらぱ2025ですよー！
All right! And so, today is also day two of SoraPa 2025!
イェーイ！み、みんな…み、今、浴びちゃった。みんなの声聞こえてる。ふふふ。
Yeah! Everyone... I just bathed in your voices. I can hear you all! *giggles*
可愛い？ありがとう！ありがとう！
Cute? Thank you! Thank you!
オレンジジュース美味しいよ。ふふふ。
Orange juice is delicious! *giggles*
えー、昨日もやりましたが、今日もね、あの、掛け声みんなでやっていきましょうね！
So, we did it yesterday, but today as well, let's do the call and response together, okay?
いやー、というわけで、はぁ、1年半ぶりなんですよ。ま、昨日ぶりだから、ま、1日ぶりですね。あははは。
Well, so, wow, it's been a year and a half. Well, since yesterday, so actually just one day. Ahahaha.
今日も2日目だよって人ー？
Who here is on their second day today as well?
今日が初めてだよって人ー？
Who here is attending for the first time today?
そもそもライブ自体初めてですよって人ー？
Who is attending a live concert for the very first time ever?
おお！じゃあ、ライブデビューですね。ありがとうございます！
Oh! So it's your live concert debut! Thank you so much!
では、全員に声出してもらいたいな！とりあえず、全員ーー！
Now, I want everyone to raise their voices! First of all, everyone!
声出せるかな？出せなかったら、手振るだけでもいいよね。
Can you raise your voice? If you can't, just waving your hands is totally fine too.
女の子ーー！おお！ありがとう！
Girls! Oh, thank you!
男の子ーー！
Boys!
未成年席ーー！おおーい！
Underage section! Oh, nice!
海外の皆さんーー！おおー！
Everyone overseas! Oh!
コメントーー！イェーイって言ってくれてる、イェーイって言ってくれてる。
Those in the comments section! They're saying 'Yeah!', they're saying 'Yeah!'.
そして、えー、左の皆さんーー！
And, everyone on the left!
右の皆さんーー！
Everyone on the right!
全員ーー！
Everyone!
いやー、最高じゃないですか！みんな声枯らす準備できてるって感じ？
Wow, isn't this the best! Does it feel like everyone is ready to lose their voices?
見えてる、見えてる。前の方、後ろの方、前の方、後ろの方。どこ見てんだろうね、ふふふ。
I can see you, I can see you. The front, the back, the front, the back. Where am I looking, right? *giggles*
はい、見えてるよー。あ、ありがとう、ありがとう、ありがとう！
Yes, I can see you! Ah, thank you, thank you, thank you!
いや、みんなのね、応援も、今日なんかラリティ率高いね。めちゃくちゃ青い。
Wow, your support today... the rarity rate seems high today. It's so blue!
なんか世界が青い。あ、ラリティじゃないのか。もしかしてあれかな？今回のライブのTシャツの人もいる？あ、そっか、Tシャツも青だもんね。
The world is so blue. Ah, it's not a rarity? Maybe it's because... is anyone wearing the T-shirt for this concert? Ah, right, the T-shirt is blue too!
すごい、ありがとうございます！もうね、みんなが外で写真撮って、『来た！今から待ち切れない！』ってやってるの、すごい見てましたから。ありがとうございます！
Amazing, thank you so much! I saw so many of you taking photos outside and posting 'I'm here! I can't wait!' I was watching closely, so thank you so much!
とね、こうやって喋ってるんですが、えー、YouTubeをご覧の皆さん！えーーー！
And while we're chatting like this... To everyone watching on YouTube! Ehhhh!
なんと！いや、まだ来たばかりなんだけど、本当に3曲しかやってないからまだ来たばかりかもしれない。
Incredibly! Well, I know you've only just joined, and we've really only done three songs so it might feel like we just started.
もの足りないなーと思う人、ぜひね、なんか、ここ、ここ、ここ、ここ、
If you feel like it's not enough, please, you know, somewhere... here, here, here, here,
どっかの概要欄があるので、そこから、配信チケット買って続きを見てもらえると、私、あんな、とっても嬉しいなと思います！
there is a description section somewhere, so if you could buy a streaming ticket from there and watch the rest, I would be so incredibly happy!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
というわけで、早速ね、おしゃべりばっかしてたらただの雑談枠になっちゃうのでね。
So, without further ado, if we just keep chatting, this will turn into a regular talking stream.
次の曲にね、行っていこうと思うんですが、まあね、昨日歌ってなくて待ってた曲あるんじゃない？次の曲は？
So I'd like to move on to the next song, but... you know, there's probably a song you've been waiting for that I didn't sing yesterday, right? The next song is...
新アルバムから、ダンスアブルな、ダンス、ダンス、ダンスな曲を歌っていこうと思います！
From the new album, I'm going to sing a danceable, dance, dance, dance song!
歌っていこうと思います！
Let's perform!
ご視聴頂きまして、ありがとうございました。
[On Screen] Thank you very much for watching.
Oh...
愛を頂戴よ
Give me love,
蜃気楼に手を伸ばして
reaching my hand out to the mirage,
秘密の夜
a secret night.
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
★ライブチケット購入はコチラ▶▶ SPWN
The free preview ends here.
★ Click here to purchase concert tickets ▶▶ SPWN